

# TRỊNH XUÂN BÌNH

.NET Developer

**16/04/1993** 

Male

<u>C</u>

Green Town Binh Tan, 3 Street, Binh Hung Hoa B Ward, Binh Tan District, Ho Chi Minh City

# **SKILLS**

API/ENTITY FRAMEWORK

HTML/CSS/JQUERY/ JAVASCRIPT

••••

MS SQL/POSTGRES SQL

BOOSTRAP/KENDOUI

••••

**REACTJS** 

DEVEXPRESS/SEMANTIC/ SYNCFUSION

MICROSOFT AZURE



#### **MAIN SKILL**

Proficient in C# programming languages.

Using DB: MS SQL/POSTGRES/MYSQL

Know Web services, REST APIs, SQL, Store procedures

Skilled in system analysis and design, knowledgeable about OOP and Design Patterns

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I possess 8 years of experience in full-stack programming with expertise in

Throughout my career, I have successfully delivered numerous projects and worked on various aspects of software development, including front-end and back-end development, database management, and API integration.

Participating in the development of software that contributes to the development of businesses and society.

#### **EDUCATION**

2011 - 2015

#### HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY AND EDUCATION

Information technology

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

6/2023 - Now

## STEPMEDIA SOFTWARE - AUVENIR | Developer

Code, implement, unit test, maintain and troubleshoot web application.

Using: .NETCORE, REACTJS, HTML, CSS, MS SQL, DEVEXPRESS, SYNCFUSION, SEMANTIC, REDIS, Microsoft Azure.

2015 - 5/2023

#### **LAC VIET CORPORATION** | Developer | Leader

Development of educational software products for educational departments, businesses.

2015 - 5/2023

**SURELRN** | Developer | Leader

Development and deploy web app manage high schools, teaching and learning online.

Using: C# MVC4, MS SQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY, KENDO UI,

**BOOTSTRAP** 

2016 - 2017

#### **SURETEST** | Developer

Development website for 10th grade exam preparation and graduation exam preparation.

Using: C# MVC4, MS SQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY, KENDO UI, BOOTSTRAP

2017 - 2018



**TEAM MANAGEMENT** 



**ENGLISH** 



# **Interests**

- Football
- Music
- Book
- o Game

## **TOOLS**

Visual studio, VS Code, SQL Server, PgAdmin, Git, TFS, Figma, Redis **OPENLRN** | Developer | Leader

Development website manage materials online.

Using: C# MVC4, MS SQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY, KENDO UI, BOOTSTRAP

2019 - 5/2023

**SURELMS** | Developer | Leader

Development and deploy web app LMS for business.

Using: C# .NETCORE MVC, POSTGRES SQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY, KENDO UI, BOOTSTRAP, KNOWGE BI

2019 - 2020

**VEBOOKS** | Developer | Leader

Development web app manage and read ebook.

Using: C# MVC, MS SQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY,

KENDO UI, BOOTSTRAP

2020 - 2022

**LANG4V** | Developer | Leader

Development web app and mobile app learn foreign languages online.

Using: C# .NETCORE MVC, POSTGRES SQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY, KENDO UI, BOOTSTRAP, IONIC APP MOBILE REACTJS

2021 - 5/2023

**BDTX** | Developer | Leader

Development and deploy web app training for high school teachers.

Using: C# .NETCORE MVC, POSTGRES SQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY, KENDO UI, BOOTSTRAP, KNOWGE BI

2022 - 5/2023

**E-READER** | Developer | Leader

Development web app and mobile app reader ebook.

Using: C# .NETCORE MVC, POSTGRES SQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY, KENDO UI, BOOTSTRAP, IONIC APP MOBILE REACTJS

2022 - 5/2023

| Developer|Leader

Development web app test for professional aptitude, majors.

Using: C# .NETCORE MVC, POSTGRES SQL/MYSQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY, KENDO UI, BOOTSTRAP

2019 - 5/2023

#### SUREBOARD, SUREMEET | Leader

Manage and support the development of tools for composing online interactive lectures and online meetings.

Using: C# .NETCORE MVC, POSTGRES SQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY, KENDO

# OB ROOTEVEAP

2015 - 2017

**LAC VIET CORPORATION** | Developer

2017 - 5/2023

**LAC VIET CORPORATION** | Developer | Leader

6/2023 - Now

**STEPMEDIA SOFTWARE** | Developer

# **REFERENCES**

Ho Cong Chien

DXC Center Director/ Deputy General Director

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

2017

**Pedagogical certificate**